{
    "question": "Percakapan tentang pekerjaan orang tua \u00a0",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "a : hello, you look so happy, whats make you&#039;re happy?<br>b : yeah, you know, my familly and i will go to bali last month!<br>a : its a good news, by the way, why you will go?<br>b : my father&#039;s get some ticket from his office<br>a: \u00a0where do you&#039;re father work?<br>b : at SA office, they meneger give some riward to their official, if they work diligent and make good job<br>a : oh, i hope you and your family have happy in bali\u00a0",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatkan-5-kalimat-either-or-dan-5-kalimat-neither-nor-346",
            "question": "Buatkan 5 kalimat either or dan 5 kalimat neither nor!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>kalimat either<br>1. Either Tommy or Tommy\u2019s friends are going to visit me tonight.\u00a0<br>2.\u00a0</span>Either Jenny or Juli has seen the Madagascar.<br>3. Either\u00a0the father\u00a0or<span>\u00a0the mother has to attend the meeting.<br></span>4.\u00a0<span>Either John or Peter received your message.<br></span>5.\u00a0Either Peter or the girls need to attend the course.<br><span><br>kalimat neither nor:<br></span><span>1.\u00a0Neither Tommy nor\u00a0Tommy\u2019s friends are going to visit me tonight.<br></span><span>2.\u00a0Neither Yayat nor two of his friends are attending the class now.<br></span>3.\u00a0Neither I nor my daughter has seen the Frozen.<br>4. <span>Neither Sarah nor Peter was to blame for the mistake.<br>5.\u00a0</span>Neither Frank nor Lilly lives in Eugene.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-teks-deskripsi-bahasa-inggris-tentang-ular-320",
            "question": "Buatlah teks deskripsi bahasa inggris tentang ular\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>The snake is one of the most successful reptiles thrive in the world . In mountains , forests , deserts , plains , farms , neighborhoods , to the sea , may be found snakes . <span>However, as is generally cold-blooded animals , snakes increasingly \nrare in cold places , such as on the tops of the mountains , in the area\n of \u200b\u200bIreland and New Zealand and the regional areas of snow or polar \ndesert .<br><br></span>Many kinds of snakes all his life wandering in the trees and almost never hit the ground . Many other types of life creeping over the surface of the soil or infiltrate infiltrate under litter or piles of rocks . <span>While most of the other living aquatic or semi - aquatic in rivers , swamps , lakes , and seas .<br><br></span>Snakes prey on various species of animals smaller than her body . Aquatic snakes prey on fish , frogs , tadpoles , fish and even eggs . Snakes and tree snakes prey on terrestrial birds , mammals , frogs , reptiles kinds of others, including its eggs . <span>Large snakes such as pythons and development can prey goats, deer , elk and even humans </span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bisa-bantu-gak-verb-2-dari-write-buy-830",
            "question": "Bisa bantu gak?\r\nverb 2 dari:\r\nwrite, buy",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "write = wrote\u00a0<br>buy = bought",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kalo write itu wrote, kalo buy itu bought",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-binggris-nya-dari-mana-saja-kamu-930",
            "question": "Apa b.inggris nya dari mana saja kamu?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "where do you come from ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bahasa-inggrisnya-motor-apa-122",
            "question": "Bahasa inggrisnya motor apa",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "bahasa inggrinya motor adalah : motorcycle\n :-)",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "bhs inggrisnya sepeda motor itu motorcycle<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "berikan-ciri-ciri-hewan-berikut-dalam-bahasa-inggris-1-hewan-mi-940",
            "question": "Berikan ciri-ciri hewan berikut dalam bahasa inggris. (1 hewan minimal 5 ciri-ciri/physical appearance)    1. Elephant\r\n2. Lion\r\n3. Tiger\r\n5. Cow\r\n6. Goat\r\n7. Cat\r\n8. Pinguin\r\n9. Chicken\r\n10. Dog",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Elephant :\u00a0has a great body, has a proboscis, has ivory, gray colored, big legs and oval<br>Lion :\u00a0brown, have fangs, claws, have thick hair on approximately heads, have 4 legs<br>Tiger :\u00a0There Orain colored striped stripes on the body, have fangs, claws, have long collapsed, has 4 legs<br>Cat :\u00a0berwarna coklat, abu abu, hitam, putih, memiliki taring, memiliki cakar, memiliki tubuh kecil panjang sepeti cita, memiliki 4 kaki, memiliki rambut di sekitar tubuh<br>Chicken :\u00a0has feathers, has beak, has 2 legs, have wings, has a comb<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "elephant :has a trunk,four legs,<br>lion:has a sharp teeth ,four legs,<br>tiger:has a black line in his body,has a sharp teeth<br>cow:eat grass,four legs ,have dots,making milk<br>goat:eat grass\u00a0<br>cat:have a mustache,four legs,has a paws<br>pinguin:has a soft and many fur,can swim,can life in cool place<br>chicken:has two legs,has a fur,cannot fly,has a wings<br>dog:has a mustache ,has four legs,eats meat<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "nama-lain-dari-verb-1-verb-2-verb-3-dan-verb-ing-pleasenee-649",
            "question": "Nama lain dari Verb 1, verb 2, verb 3, dan verb-ing Please....Need banget&gt;_&lt;",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "v1 = bare infinitive<br>v2 = past tense<br>v3 = past participle<br>ving = present participle",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tuliskan-percakapan-binggris-2-orang-tentang-makanan-indonesia-690",
            "question": "Tuliskan percakapan\u00a0b.inggris 2 orang\u00a0tentang makanan indonesia !",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "waiter : can i take your order please<br>costumer : i would one rice<br>waiter : what do you want to drink with your rice ?<br>costumer : i want a glass tea<br>waiter : would you like anything else ?<br>costumer : i;d like the bill please ?<br>waiter : here you are<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "membuat-pidato-bahasa-inggris-tentang-menjaga-kebersihan-lingkung-502",
            "question": "Membuat pidato bahasa inggris tentang menjaga kebersihan lingkungan sekolah",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Assalamualaikum wr wb.<br>and good afternoon<br>The Honourable mothers and fathers who are present in this place<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 first of all I would like say thank to the Almighty God who has given us a good healt so we can join in this nice place.<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 The second time, do not forget I said thank to the our Prophet Muhammad Saw had brought us from the realm of darkness into the lightness<br>In addition, I would like say thank to the audience for allowing me to deliver my speech with the theme of keeping the environment clean<br>well, my beloved brothers and sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Keeping the environment clean is a way and the actions we can do to be able to obtain the beauty and the beauty of the environment, other than that if we always keep the environment around us, our environment will be maintained and healthy so that we can all farthest from various diseases.<br>A healthy environment would be more fun and comfortable to live in the neighborhood of a dirty\u00a0 filled with garbage strewn everywhere.<br>My beloved brothers and Sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 We have seen so many benefits that can be obtained if we keep the environment clean, therefore we as a society that cares about the environment, let us together to preserve the environment around us to look comfortable and cool in the view<br>and always a pleasant environment.</span><span>My beloved Brothers and Sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 So what can I say, if there are sentences that are less pleasing to you, I apologize, because there is no ivory that is not going to crack and there would be no human beings make mistakes.<br>thank you for your attention and wasalamualaikum wr wb.<br></span><span><br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-yang-dimaksud-dengan-past-tense-dan-beri-contohnya-634",
            "question": "Apa yang dimaksud dengan Past Tense dan beri contohnya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Dalam bahasa Inggris ada Past Tense, sedangkan bahasa Indonesia kalaupun ada tak perlu dipelajari, karena kata kerjanya tidak berubah. Seperti\u00a0Present Tense, maka\u00a0Past Tense\u00a0ini pun terbagi 4: Ada yang Simple Past atau disebut Past Tense saja, ada yang\u00a0Past Continuous Tense, Past Prefect Tense dan\u00a0Past Perfect Continuous Tense.</span>Inti dari Past Tense adalah untuk menyatakan peristiwa yang telah \u201cLampau\u201d. Lampau disini tak harus sudah lama-lama amat juga, pokoknya sudah berlalu, sudah lewat. Itulah penekanannya. Mungkin kemarin, satu jam lalu, 2 tahun lalu, 2 abad yang lalu, dan sebagainya. Semua itu sudah \u201cPast\u201d. Setelah membaca uraian ini Anda pasti faham lebih dalam. Pasang mata pasang telinga dan kuatkan niat ya, hehe..Rumus Past Tense:\nPositif: S + V2\nNegatif: S + did not + V1\nTanya: Did + S + V1\n<span>Ingat, V2 maksud saya adalah Kata Kerja atau Verb bentuk ke-2. Tentang kata kerja dapat Anda baca di\u00a0Kata Kerja</span><span>Rumus Past Tense Rumit?<br>Benar! eh tidak, lanjutkan saja bacanya..</span><span>Anda resepkan dulu bahwa kata kerja bantu \u201cDO\u201d bentuk present\u00a0DO, bentuk keduanya (Bentuk Past) adalah\u00a0DID. Kalau Present kan: I do not\u2026 maka Past nya: I did not\u2026.</span><span>Yang barusan saya terangkan diatas tadi akan memudahkan Anda mempelajari\u00a0Past Tense\u00a0ini untuk Kalimat yang Negatif dan Kalimat Tanya. Ingat saja DO jadi DID. inga.. inga\u2026 hehe..</span><span>Contoh Kalimat Past Tense:<br>-I launched this blog on july 14th 2009</span><span>Artinya:<br>Saya meluncurkan atau launching blog ini tanggal 14 juli 2009.<br>Sudah lewat kan?</span>Kata kerjanya bentuk kedua \u201claunched\u201d, ini tergolong kata kerja beraturan, tinggal tambahkan ED di belakang launch.<span>Anda ingin punya blog sendiri seperti milik saya ini? Do you want to have your own blog like this? Wah mudah sekali. Dengan blog kita bisa menghasilkan bejibun uang\u00a0\u00a0Anda bisa berlangganan newsletter saya dulu disini ya:\u00a0Bisnis24.com</span><span>Ok kita lanjutkan tentang\u00a0Paste Tense\u00a0ini ya.</span>Contoh lagi:Kita akan pakai kata kerja bentuk 1-2-3 berikut:<span>see \u2013 saw \u2013 seen (melihat)<br>buy \u2013 bought- bought (membeli)<br>go \u2013 went \u2013 gone (pergi)</span><span>-I saw her standing there (Saya lihat dia berdiri disana).<br>-My Father bought this car last year<br>-They went to Tokyo last month<br>-She went home two minutes ago</span>Semua itu sudah terjadi, sudah melihat, membeli mobilnya juga tahun lalu, ke Tokyonya bulan lalu, pulangnya (went home) juga 2 menit yang lalu. Kita gunakan Past Tense. Faham ya?Kalimat Negatif Past TenseSesuai rumusnya: S + did + not + V1Perhatikan dengan seksama, Kata kerjanya berubah lagi menjadi bentuk pertama (V1). Lalu kata kerja bentuk past-nya kemana? Pindah ke DID nya itu. Tadi kan diatas sudah saya bilang:V1 -V2 \u2013 V3: Do \u2013 Did \u2013 DoneJadi kita pakai \u201cDid\u201d. Karena negatif maka tambah \u201cNot\u201d. Jadi Did Not! hehe..<span>Kalimat positif tadi, kita jadikan negatif:<br>-I saw her standing there<br>Menjadi: I did not see her standing there</span><span>Lihatlah\u00a0saw\u00a0jadi\u00a0see\u00a0lagi. See-saw-seen kan bentuk kata kerjanya?</span><span>Yes benar, berurusan dengan Past Tense maka Anda perlu mempunyai banyak perbendaharaan\u00a0Kata Kerja.</span><span>Positif: My Father bought this car last year<br>Negatif: My Father did not BUY this car last year</span><span>Anda coba yang dua ini ya:<br>-They went to Tokyo last month. Jadi \u2026.<br>-She went home two minutes ago. Jadi \u2026.</span>Kalimat Tanya Past TenseKalau Anda sudah tau kalimat negatif Past Tense maka kalimat tanya tinggal dibalik mawon, DID nya di depan Subject.<span>Positif: My Father bought this car last year<br>Tanya: Did My Father BUY this car last year</span><span>Anda coba yang dua ini ya:<br>-They went to Tokyo last month. Jadi \u2026.<br>-She went home two minutes ago. Jadi \u2026.</span>Boleh saja Anda tambahkan dengan Where, When, Why dan sebagainya seperti ini:<span>-When did my father buy this car?<br>-Why did they go to tokyo?</span>Demikianlah tentang Past Tense.<span>Best Regards<br>Mufli</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Inti dari Past Tense adalah untuk menyatakan peristiwa yang telah \n\u201cLampau\u201d. Lampau disini tak harus sudah lama-lama amat juga, pokoknya \nsudah berlalu, sudah lewat. Itulah penekanannya. Mungkin kemarin, satu \njam lalu, 2 tahun lalu, 2 abad yang lalu, dan sebagainya. Semua itu \nsudah \u201cPast\u201d. Setelah membaca uraian ini Anda pasti faham lebih dalam. \nPasang mata pasang telinga dan kuatkan niat ya, hehe..\nRumus Past Tense:\nPositif: S + V2\nNegatif: S + did not + V1\nTanya: Did + S + V1\n\n<span>Ingat, V2 maksud saya adalah Kata Kerja atau Verb bentuk ke-2. Tentang kata kerja dapat Anda baca di Kata Kerja<br><br></span>Contoh Kalimat Past Tense:<br>\n-I launched this blog on july 14th 2009<br>-I saw her standing there (Saya lihat dia berdiri disana).<br>\n-My Father bought this car last year<br>\n-They went to Tokyo last month<br>\n-She went home two minutes ago<br><span><br>:)<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}